A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP), SG 3, Series 14 FA1475
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP), 1925-2006; 14
  - Symposiums and Surveys, 6
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Participant Confirmation Letters, 1998 October (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Plenary - Senator John D. Rockefeller IV, 1998 October (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Schedule and Agenda, 1998 October (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Karen Davis Closing Remarks, 1998 October (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Moderator Crib Sheets, 1998 October (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Participants List, 1998 October (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - The Carlton Hotel, 1998 October (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Planning Meeting, 1997-1999 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Hotel and Menu (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Conference Calls (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Draft Invitation Letters (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - The Carlton Hotel (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - New Briefing Corrrespondence (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - New Briefing Materials (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - John Iglehart (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Seating Arrangements (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Australia (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Canada (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - United Kingdom (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - United States (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - New Zealand (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Press Materials, 1998 October (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Project Hope - Grant 970947, 1997-2000 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Project Hope - Grant 970947 - Health Affairs - Karen Davis Article (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Project Hope - Grant 970947 - Grant Contract, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Project Hope - Grant 970947 - Letter of Acceptance (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Project Hope - Grant 970947 - Health Affairs, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Project Hope - Grant 970947 - Budget, 1997-1999 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Margaret E. Mahoney (MEM) Symposium, 1998-1999 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - 1999 Ditchley-MEM Symposium, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Louis Harris and Associates - International Health Policy Survey, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - 1998 International Health Policy Survey (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - International Health Policy Survey - Correspondence, Email (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - International Health Policy Survey - Robert Blendon, 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - International Health Policy Survey - Contract, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - International Health Policy Survey - Findings, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - International Health Policy Survey, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - International Health Policy Survey - Draft Surveys, 1997-1998 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - 1998 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - OECD Draft Chart Books, 1997-1998 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - 1998 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - International Data Comparison, 1997-1998 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - 1998 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - International Data Comparison - Letter of Acceptance, 1997-1999 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - 1998 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - International Data Comparison - The World Bank, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - 1998 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - International Data Comparison - Budget (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - 1998 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - International Data Comparison - Grant Contract (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - 1998 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - International Data Comparison - OECD Chart Book (Box 62, Folder 2-3)
    - 1998 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - International Data Comparison - OECD Publications, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - 1998 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - Gerard Anderson - Johns Hopkins University (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Minister of Health Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 3-4)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Agenda (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Papers (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Papers (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Invitation Letters (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Thank You Letters (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Planning Meeting, 1999 February (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Planning Meeting, 1999 February (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Osborn's Notes from Symposium Speakers (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Keynote Speaker (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Blair House (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis Hotel (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - First Follow Up Participants List (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Background Readings (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors Articles (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - International Longevity Center, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Speakers (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors Papers (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Participant List (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors Papers (Box 69, Folder 2-4)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors Papers (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - 1999 Chart Book Comments (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
    - 1999 Cross National Comparison of Health Data Systems - Chart Book, 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 3-5)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Meeting (980885), 1999 March 15 (Box 84, Folder 4-5)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Meeting (980885), 1999 March 15 (Box 85, Folder 1-3)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Meeting, 2000 July 17-18 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Meeting, 2000 July 17-18 (Box 86, Folder 1-4)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Technical Subcommittee Meeting, 2001 June 26-27 (Box 87, Folder 1-4)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Meeting, 2002 January 8-9 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Meeting, 2002 January 8-9 (Box 88, Folder 1-3)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Health Affairs Article, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Meeting, 2002 January 8-9 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Technical Subcommittee Meeting, 2003 January 14-15 (Box 89, Folder 2-4)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Ministers Reports - Drafts, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 1-2)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Ministers Reports - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 3-4)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2002 June 4-5 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2002 June 4-5 (Box 100, Folder 1-4)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2002 June 4-5 (Box 101, Folder 1-3)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2002 September 17-18 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2002 September 17-18 (Box 102, Folder 1-5)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2000 July 17-18 (Box 103, Folder 1-4)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Hotel, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Technical Subcomittee, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 4-5)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Speaker Invitation Letters, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Press Coverage, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Meeting Seating Arrangements, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Thank You Letters, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Participant Invite Letters, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Participant Invite Lists, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Secy. Tommy Thompson, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Blair House, 2000-2001 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Cover and Spine, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Mark Merlis Contract Letter, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Papers (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - New Zealand (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Australia (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - St. Regis Hotel (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - AV Requirements (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Ministers Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Correspondence with Sec. Thompson, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Survey - Chart Pack (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Budget, Expenses, 2000-2001 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Blair House (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - 2001 International Survey - Final Survey Draft (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - 2000 International Survey - Final Survey Draft (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - 2000 International Survey - Slide Presentation (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - 2000 International Survey - Health Affairs Article (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - 2000 International Survey - Press Briefing (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - 1999 International Survey - Press Release (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - 1999 International Survey - Health Affairs Article (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - 1999 International Survey - Final Survey Draft (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - 1998 International Survey - Press Release (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - 1998 International Survey - Final Survey Draft (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - 1998 International Survey - Health Affairs Article (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - 2001 Multinational Health Policy Survey, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 16-17)
    - 2001 Multinational Health Policy Survey - Proposal (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - 2001 Multinational Health Policy Survey - Highlights (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - 2001 Multinational Health Policy Survey - Deliverables (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - 2001 Multinational Health Policy Survey - Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - 2001 Health Affairs-Project HOPE - Budget (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - 2001 Health Affairs-Project HOPE - Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - 2001 Health Affairs-Project HOPE - Proposal (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2001 June 26 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - 2000 Ditchley - US-UK Collaboration (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - 2000 Ditchley - Budget (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - 2000 Ditchley Conference - Ezekiel Emanuel - Travel and Honoraria (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - 2000 Ditchley Conference - Commissioned Papers (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - 2000 Ditchley Conference - Authors (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - 2000 Ditchley-MEM Symposium (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - 2000 Ditchley - Correspondence (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - 2000 Ditchley Conference - Papers (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - 2000 Ditchley - Nuffield Trust (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - 2000 Ditchley - Background Papers (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - 2000 Ditchley - Participants (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - 2000 Ditchley - Proposal and LOA (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - 2000 Ditchley - Speaker's Letters (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - 2000 Ditchley - Nuffield Trust (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - 2000 Ditchley Conference - UK Participant Letters (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - 2000 Ditchley Conference - US Participant Letters (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - 2000 Ditchley Conference - Authors Letters (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality - Budget (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality - Draft Papers (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality - Papers, Reports (Box 121, Folder 1-2)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality - Draft Papers (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality (Box 122, Folder 1-2)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality - Proposal (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality - Correspondence (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality - Budget (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill - UK Participant Invite Letters (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill - US Participant Invite Letters, 2001 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration - Travel Memos to All U.S. (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill - US Participant Invite Letters (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration - Travel Memos to All U.S. (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill - UK Participant Invite Letters (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill - US Speaker Invite Letters (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill - Travel Questionnaire (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill - UK Speaker Invite Letters (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration on Quality - Correspondence (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration - Binder Covers and Spine (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill - UK Speaker Invite Letters (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill - US Speaker Invite Letters (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Carolyn Tuohy (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Julian LeGrand (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Don Berwick (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Ronald Paterson (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Peter Smith (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Senator Michael Kirby (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Bruce Siegel (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Colin Tukuitonga (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Steepher Leeder (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Aidan Halligan (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Don Nutbeam (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Uwe Reinhardt (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Briefing Materials (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - 2001 International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Proposal (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - 2001 International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Technical Subcommittee (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - 2002 International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Agenda, Participants, 2001 January 8 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - 2001 International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Technical Subcommittee (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - 2002 International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Correspondence, 2001 January 8 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - 2001 IHP Coordinating Committee - List-Terms (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - 2001 IHP Coordinating Committee - Correspondence (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators Meeting, 2002 (Box 126, Folder 1-2)
    - 2000 Coordinating Committee - Member List (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - 2000 Coordinating Committee - Correspondence (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - 1999 IHP Coordinating Committee Meeting, 1999 October 22 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - 1999 IHP Coordinating Committee - General Correspondence (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - 1999 Coordinating Committee - Members List (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - 1999 IHP Coordinating Committee - Thank You Letters (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - 2001 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Mark Merlis Contract Letter (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - 1997 IHP Coordinating Committee (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Coordinating Committee Meeting, 1998 February 6 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - 1998 IHP Coordinating Committee - General Correspondence (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - 1998 IHP Coordinating Committee - Thank You Letters (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy, 1998 October 21-23 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - 2001 Multinational Health Policy Survey - Budget (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - 2001 Multinational Health Policy Survey - Proposal (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - 2001 Multinational Health Policy Survey - Comments (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - 2001 Multinational Health Policy Survey - Deliverables (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - 2001 Health Affairs-Project HOPE - Correspondence (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - 2001 Health Affairs-Project HOPE - Proposal (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - 2001 Health Affairs-Project HOPE - Budget (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - 2001 Health Affairs-Project HOPE - Deliverables (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - 2000-2001 IHP Program Plan (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - 2001 IHP Program Plan (Box 144, Folder 4-5)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Conference Notebook, 1997-1998 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Papers, 1997-1998 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Planning, 1997-1998 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - OECD Data Analysis - Anderson-Jhu Board Proposal, 2003 November 11 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Pennyhill Park 2004 - Board Proposal 2003, 2003 November (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Health Affairs 2004 - Board Proposal 2003, 2003 November 11 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - 2002 Pennyhill Park (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - 2003 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Hospitals and Health Care Delivery Systems - Transcription, 2003 October 22 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - International Health Policy and Reform Network - Issue Briefs, 2003 September (Box 162, Folder 1-3)
    - Health Care Systems in Transition, 2000 (Box 162, Folder 4-5)
    - Health Care Systems in Transition, 2000 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - 2004 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Primary Health Care: Spotlight on Innovation and Reform - Transcription, 2004 October 22-24 (Box 163, Folder 2-3)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Quality and Innovation Issues: Strategy and Implications for Policy - Transcription, 2000 October 11-13 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - 2000 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Quality and Innovation Issues: Strategy and Implications for Policy - Transcription, 2000 October 11-13 (Box 164, Folder 1-2)
    - 1999 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Financing, Delivery and Ensuring Quality of Health and Long-Term Care for An Aging Population - Transcription, 1999 October 20-22 (Box 164, Folder 3-4)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Costs, Quality and Equity: Current Issues and Future Prospects - Transcription, 1998 October 21-23 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - 1999 International Symposum on Health Care Policy - Planning Meeting, 1999 February 1 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - 1999 International Symposum on Health Care Policy - Handouts (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - 1999 IHP Cross National Aging Survey (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - 1999 International Symposum on Health Care Policy - Denmark Papers (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - 1999 AUS-NZ Health Services Research Conference (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Ditchley III (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - 2001 US-UK Collaboration - Penny Hill Park - Biographies (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - AHSR Binational Research Conference, Canada-U.S., Chicago, 1999 June 26 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Bipartisan Congressional Health Policy Conference, 2006 January 12-14 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Nuffield Trust-Commonwealth Fund Symposium, 2004 May 20 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Margaret E. Mahoney (MEM) Lecture and Symposium, New York Academy of Medicine, 1998 May 19 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - International Working Group on Quality Indicators - Subcommittee Meeting, 2001 July 17-18 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - 2003 International Working Group on Quality Indicators, 2003 October 1 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - 2005 DELSA-HEA-HCQ - Health Care Quality Indicators Meeting, Paris, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - 2004 OECD Health Technical Papers, Volume 14 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - OECD Health Care Quality Indicators Meetings, Paris, 2006 October 16-18 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Health Care Quality Indicators Project - Initial Indicators Report, Working Paper No. 22 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - 2006 International Symposium on Health Care Policy, 1979 (Box 184, Folder 1-4)
    - 2006 International Symposium on Health Care Policy, 2006 November 1-3 (Box 185, Folder 1-2)
    - 2004 International Symposium on Health Care Policy, 2004 October (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Ian Axford (New Zealand) Fellowships in Public Policy, 7
    - Ian Axford (New Zealand) Fellowships in Public Policy - Selection Committee, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 4-6)